flyinmiata.com 2019-07-09

# Flyin' Miata Privacy Policy

## Short version:

We don't share your information with anyone else for their own purposes. We hate that as much as you do.

## Long version

This privacy policy sets out how Flyin' Miata uses and protects any information that you give Flyin' Miata when you use this website. Flyin' Miata is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Flyin' Miata may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect in our webstore see the List of cookies we collect section.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We will use this information to contact you about your orders, both to ensure accuracy beforehand and with a followup to ensure you are satisfied.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * If you have asked us to do so, we may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * We may mail you a printed catalog once or twice a year unless you ask us not to.
  * We may share information with service providers under contract who help with parts of our business operations, such as fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, and technology services.
  * We may share your information with service providers who assist us with serving relevant ads for our own products to you. We require by contract that our service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

**We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties for their own use.  
**

We may provide some information to third parties in order to serve you advertisements for our own products on other websites at our request. Any data used to serve targeted advertisements is de-identified and is not used to personally or directly identify you. [Click here to adjust your advertising preferences](http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false) for us and for others.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 499 35 Rd Palisade, CO 81526 USA.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | Your sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.
